https://www.syntax.co.uk/privacy-policy

IT Support & Outsourcing
Remote Working Solutions (Covid-19)
Microsoft Office 365 Services
Microsoft Teams – Consulting, Integration and Support Service
IT Support & Outsourcing
Remote Working Solutions (Covid-19)
Microsoft Office 365 Services
Microsoft Teams – Consulting, Integration and Support Service
Privacy Policy
By accessing this page and using the Web Site www.syntax.co.uk you signify your acceptance of our Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our site. Your continued use of the Syntax Integration Limited site following the posting of changes to these terms will mean that you accept these changes.
1.0 General
Syntax Integration Limited trading as Syntax (“we”, “us” or “Syntax”) take the privacy of your information very seriously.
This Privacy Notice is designed to explain our practices regarding the collection, use and disclosure of personal information we may hold about clients and customers, suppliers, and other third parties.
This privacy notice does not apply to information we hold in relation to our staff and contractors which is covered by a separate privacy notice.
This notice applies to any personal information we hold about individuals (other than staff), whether they are a client or otherwise. In this notice “you” refers to any individual whose personal data we hold or process.
This notice is governed by the EU General Data Protection Regulation (the “GDPR”) from 25 May 2018.
This notice applies to personal data we hold about you. “Personal data” means information that relates to you as an identified or identifiable person.
2.0 Legal basis on which we process personal data
2.1 Personal data we hold about you will be lawfully processed based on one of the following legal reasons (known as a “legal basis”):
2.1.1 Because the processing is necessary for a “legitimate interest”, a legitimate interest in this context means a valid interest we have, or a third party has, in processing your personal data which is not overridden by your interests in data privacy and security;
2.1.2 Because the processing is necessary in order for us to comply with our obligations under a contract between you or your employer and us; or;
2.1.3 Because you have consented to the processing.
3.0 Personal data which we collect
3.1 We may collect and process the following personal data about you:
3.1.1 Contact information which we hold because you are employed or engaged by a client of ours, or have registered an interested in finding out more about our services (for instance your email address or contact telephone number) (“Client Contact Information”);
3.1.2 Any other personal information which you provide to us as your client or in your capacity as an employee of our client, as part of our service provision (“Validation Information”);
3.1.3 Contact information which we hold because you are a third party relevant to the services we provide to our clients (you may for example be a supplier or vendor) (“Third Party Contact Information”);
3.1.4 Records of emails and other correspondence between you and us and our employees (“Communication Information”);
3.1.5 Other public information which is generally available (“Public Information”).
You do not have to supply any personal information to us and you may withdraw our authority to process your personal data at any time.
4.0 How we process your Personal Data
Purpose/Activity
Type of data
Lawful basis for processing
When you or your employer engage us to provide services
Client Contact Information
Validation Information
Performance of a contract
Necessary for our legitimate interests (to establish necessary information about you in order to provide our services).
When we provide services to you / your employer
Client Contact Information
Validation Information
Communication Information
Third Party Contact Information
Performance of a contract
When we communicate with third parties on behalf of our clients in the provision of our services
Client Contact Information
Third Party Information
Performance of a contract
To manage and administer our relationship with you as a client or third party
Client Contact Information
Third Party Contact Information
Performance of a contract
Dealing with a complaint or services enquiry
Client Contact Information
Communication Information
Invite you to events on behalf of our clients or to general events in given areas of interest or concern
Client Contact Information
Third Party Information
5.0 Data Retention
Our current data retention policy is to delete or destroy (to the extent that we are able to) the personal data we hold about you in accordance with the following;
Category of personal data
Length of retention
Records relevant for tax purposes
8 years from the end of the tax year to which the records relate
Personal data processed in relation to a contract between you (or your employer) and us
7 years from the end of our contract with you or your employer
Personal data held on general contact databases
3 years from the last date on which you have interacted with us
5.1 For any category of personal data not specifically defined in this Notice, and unless otherwise specified by applicable law, the required retention period for any personal data will be deemed to be 7 years from the date of receipt by us of that data.
5.2 The retention periods stated in this Notice can be prolonged or shortened as may be required (for example, in the event that legal proceedings apply to the data or if there is an on-going investigation into the data).
5.3 We review the personal data (and the categories of personal data) we are holding on a regular basis to ensure the data we are holding is still relevant to our business and is accurate. If we discover that certain data we are holding is no longer necessary or accurate, we will take reasonable steps to correct or delete this data as may be required.
6.0 Sharing your information
We do not disclose personal information you provide to any third parties other than as follows:
6.1 As part of the provision of services we may disclose information to suppliers, and third parties as part of the performance of a contract (although we will not disclose personal contact information without your consent);
6.2 If we are sub-contracting services to a third party we may provide information to that third party in order to provide the relevant services;
6.3 if we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation (for example, if required to do so by a court order or for the purposes of prevention of fraud or other crime);
6.4 in order to enforce any terms or agreements for our services;
6.5 to protect our rights, property and safety, or the rights, property and safety of our users or any other third parties. This includes exchanging information for the purposes of fraud protection.
Other than as set out above, we will not disclose any of your personal information unless you give us permission to do so. If we do supply your personal information to a third party we will take steps to ensure that your privacy rights are protected and that third party complies with the terms of this notice.
7.0 Security
7.1 We will take all reasonable steps to ensure that appropriate technical and organisational measures are carried out in order to safeguard the information we collect from you and protect against unlawful access and accidental loss or damage.
7.2 This notice and our procedures for handling personal data will be reviewed as necessary.
7.3 All SARs and other requests or notifications in respect of your above rights must be sent to us in writing to Syntax Integration Limited, FAO Data Protection Manager, 15-16 Seymour Mews, London, W1H 6BG or enquiries@syntax.co.uk.
7.4 We will endeavour to comply with such requests as soon as possible but in any event we will comply within one month of receipt (unless a longer period of time to respond is reasonable by virtue of the complexity or number of your requests).
8.0 Data Breaches
If personal data we hold about you is subject to a breach or unauthorised disclosure or access, we will report this to the Information Commissioner’s Office (ICO) and/or our data protection manager or officer (if an officer has been appointed).
If a breach is likely to result in a risk to your data rights and freedom, we will notify you as soon as possible.
9.0 Transferring your information outside Europe
9.1 Our services are international in nature. As part of the services we provide information may be transferred to, processed and stored at, countries or international organisations outside of the EEA.
9.2 We will not transfer any data in a systematic way outside of the EEA but there may be circumstances in which certain personal information is transferred outside of the EEA, in particular:
9.3 We may communicate with individuals or organisations outside of the EEA in delivering our services, those communications may include personal information (such as contact information);
9.4 We may be required to provide certain personal information as part of a legal reporting obligation to an entity outside the EEA (for example the US Federal Government) and some of that information may be made public;
9.5 From time to time your information may be stored in devices which are used by our staff outside of the EEA (but staff will be subject to our cyber-security policies).
9.6 If we transfer your information outside of the EEA, and the third country or international organisation in question has not been deemed by the EU Commission to have adequate data protection laws, we will provide appropriate safeguards and your privacy rights will continue to be enforceable against us as outlined in this notice.
Request a call back
For more information speak to one of
our advisors. Simply fill in your
details and we will call you back.
Your Name
Your Number
We are here to help
If you have questions or need a quick
quote. Talk to our team.
Call us on
020 7307 5008
or fill in the form to receive a quote.
QUICK QUOTE
Syntax IT Support London
4.9
Azam Ali 12:47 27 Feb 20
Good products and well presented
Michael Silva 08:22 20 Oct 19
Great service! Thank you
L Pattinson 12:27 19 Aug 19
An excellent company to work with. 10 out of 10
Matt McKenna 15:05 15 Aug 19
The best IT support company we've ever used. Our online business was in desperate need of some help to secure our internal network and revise our Microsoft set up. Syntax delivered that and have been very accommodating with all our requests.
Jonathan Davies 14:07 15 Aug 19
We approached Syntax IT Support London as we were having issues from our current IT outsourcing provider that wasn't meeting our needs and requirements. Having a business that is very IT led and dependent means that downtime or issues with systems has a direct knock on affect to all areas of the business. We were very pleased with their refreshing approach to how to handle our operations and how they would implement these changes. It's now been over 2 months with Syntax and everyone has been very easy and professional and dramatically changed our business for the better. We are now looking at Office 365 migration with them over the next 3 months as we believe we will really benefit from these recommendations. We have now worked with 2 other well known IT support providers in London and Syntax stand out above every other company we've tried or spoken with. We are currently very happy with their service and won't be going elsewhere.
Accounts Department 09:46 27 Jun 19
Syntax helped transform and streamline our IT processes. As a growing business we needed a company that could help connect our office systems in to the cloud. We now have a much easier, reliable and set up. Their 24/7 IT support service means we're never alone or have issues that can't be fixed immediately.
Tom Smith 16:19 20 Mar 19
Syntax IT Support London transformed our operation and streamlined our IT processes. Their knowledge regarding g cloud, office 365 is second to none.
sdv h 07:03 17 Oct 17
very good it support company
Sarah Mann 08:45 04 Apr 17
After being let down by our previous IT support company we decided to look for a new provider that could offer the immediate support we require. After meeting with Syntax we knew that we had found the right company to support our growing business needs. We have been using Syntax Integration for more than 10 months and their team of IT support specialists have been fantastic. Look no further!
Blaise Rochester 08:44 04 Apr 17
We have been using Syntax Integration for over 5 months since we changed from our last provider. We have found them to be very approachable and have correct many issues including our out dated server for media storage.
I would have no hesitation in recommending them to any one who is looking to get a first rate service.
Samantha Roberts 21:10 17 Mar 17
Thank you Syntax we really appreciate all you've done to help
Peter Wainright 13:36 13 Mar 17
Our business relies heavily on our IT infrastructure and ensuring that our systems are working correctly at all times. Previously we had employed 3 IT technicians who handled the day to day business but as our business grew so did our demands in terms of support and testing. In order to scale our business further we needed to find an IT company who could work with our team and ensure that our needs were met. We have been using Syntax for over 5 months and we couldn't be happier with the service they have provided. We are now running Office 365 and Azure and it has massively streamlined out business.
Tom Peary 21:08 14 May 16
Look after all my IT issues. When our business grew and needed to migrate our office 365 to the cloud syntax made it simple and stress free
Steve Bruce 13:17 12 Feb 16
Syntax offer a transparent and streamlined IT service which our business could not operate properly without. We are very happy with the service and will continue to use.
Mark Struder 20:22 11 Feb 13
Our business is very dependent on our IT infrastructure, and it's extremely important that we have a reliable provider who can deliver the goods when it is most needed, even if this is out of hours. Excellent service!
Lindsay Wooler 13:32 11 Feb 13
A professional IT support from Syntax Integration Ltd is what we have had for 2 years. We will continue to recommend them to all our of network and clients due to their superior level of support service. We have used other London IT companies but have never been 100% satisfied until now - their ervices are unrivalled in our books.
Philip Pollock 10:58 20 Sep 10
We outgrew our exiting IT support provider and tried Syntax instead. So far they have been responsive, professional and helpful.
Next Reviews
© Syntax Integration 2019 | Website designed by Keri Newman Design LimitedSyntax Integration Ltd. Syntax House, 15-16 Seymour Mews London W1H 6BG. 020 7307 5008 |
Find us on Google Maps and Google+ Home | About Syntax |Services |
Technologies | Customers | News & Events
| FAQ | Contact Us | IT Support London
| Terms | Privacy |
Site Map | RSS
